analdin.com 2018-10-14

# Analdin.com

Privacy Policy 

Our Privacy Policy has been updated in order to comply with the new EU law by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your access to and use of our Website signifies that you have read, understand and agree to all terms within this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of this privacy policy or our terms, please do not access or continue to use our Website or otherwise submit your personal data. 

We at Analdin.com ("Website") take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your personal data. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please see “Contact Information” below for information on how to contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the collection and processing of personal data carried out by our Website. We do not control third-party websites you may access from Analdin.com and are not responsible for their privacy statements. 

We may collect, use and store several types of personal data to the extent it is necessary to provide users with our service: 

Persons who visit the Website without logging in or registering “unregistered users” 

  * · Technical Data includes pseudonymized internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
  * · Usage Data includes aggregated information about how you use our Website, products, and services. 

Persons who choose to create an account “registered users” 

  * · Identity Data includes a username or similar identifier, date of birth and gender.
  * · Contact Data includes email address.
  * · Technical Data includes pseudonymized internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
  * · User Submitted Data includes data collected at your direction for a specific function, for example, your username and password, your preferences, feedback, and comments.
  * · Usage Data includes information about how you use our Website, products, and services.
  * · Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We may also collect and process an aggregated data to generate statistics about our users that may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. We do not collect special categories of Personal Information about you (race or ethnicity, religious beliefs, political opinions, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). 

Methods to Collect Personal Information: 

  * 1\. Direct interactions. Search queries on our Website, filling in forms on our Website, subscribing to our service, posting materials, taking part in surveys, reporting a problem with our Website etc Automated technologies or interactions. We use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment and browsing actions, including IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information, search terms, and cookie information
  * 2\. Cookies (or browser cookies). Cookies do not store personal information. We only collect information related to the preferences of the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We do not require that you accept cookies and you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser’s privacy settings. However, if you block cookies, some functionality on our Website may be disabled and you may be unable to log in. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your internet browser’s “help” file.
  * 3\. Gifs: We use a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.
  * 4.Analytics. We use third-party analytics and advertising tools and technologies, in particular, Google Analytics provided by Google, Inc., USA (“Google”).
  * Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers and content providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our website does not provide any Personal Information to these third parties. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

How We Use Your Personal Data: 

We will only use your personal data when the applicable local law allows us to. Most commonly, in the following circumstances: To perform the services provided to you under our Term and Conditions, and any other agreement that you have with us. Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests. Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. Where you declare your valid consent to use it.

Purposes for Which We Use Your Personal Information: 

  * · Provision of services, customer management, customization of content for registered members only; 
  * · Analytics: to determine unique users, to monitor a total number of visitors, pages viewed, demographic patterns; 
  * · Functionality and security: to diagnose or fix technology problems, and to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraud, illegal activities, or intellectual property infringement; 
  * · Compliance: to enforce our terms and conditions and to comply with our legal obligations; 

We do not disclose your Personal Information except in the limited circumstances 

* *to our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf; 

* *to legal successors (in a case of a Website liquidation, sale, transfer or similar proceeding); 

* *to regulators, law enforcement when we reasonably believe such disclosure is needed to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request,help investigation of potential violations, detect and prevent illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues, protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; or to maintain and protect the security and integrity of our Website. 

* Our Policy Towards Minors: Our Website is not directed to persons under the age of 18 or the applicable age of majority in the jurisdiction from which the Website is accessed and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at support@analdin.com. If we become aware that a minor has provided us with Personal Information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate that person’s account. 

No Error Free Performance: We do not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. We shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy. 

Confidentiality and Security: Our Website commits to taking all the necessary measures to prevent and secure the data that’s collected and treated, preventing them from being damaged, destroyed or stolen. However, we don’t control every risk associated with internet usage, so there are always risks associated with the usage of internet and data sharing online. 

Your Rights to Request, Change or Delete Your Data: According to the law in force, the users have the right to access their personal data free of costs anytime they want, and have the right to change or delete their personal data free of costs anytime they want. We can also provide to our users, in a digital format, a copy of their personal data explaining what have we collected, where we’re using it and who has access to it. 

Contact Information: If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us at support@analdin.com. 

You may also contact us at Blanc & Noir Ltd, Tenancy 10, Marina House, Eden Island, Seychelles. GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation law in the European Union effective May 25, 2018, users can request a copy of their personal data as well as get Website to delete their personal data.
